So, you're at the restaurant and you want to impress your lady.
So, I'm Robert Segundo and I'm going to teach you how to make a paper rose.
If we look down here, we can see I've just a regular napkin.
What I'm going to do, is I'm going to take it.
I'm going to go ahead and I'm going to unfold it.
Open it all the way.
Now, this one is kind of an odd shape.
So, what I'm going to do is I'm going to kind of fold down a little bit here at the top.
This is going to be for the petals at the top.
And, what I like to do is fold it back up like so.
Basically, we're just going to take this and roll this up like so.
Kind of keep this open end here we'll see with your fingers.
Just going to come down here below it.
Just going to twist it up just a little bit.
Now, this flap here we're going to kind of hold it out as well while we twist the rest of it up.
This is great when you're out and you bought your lady that happy meal and you really want to impress her with a little flower afterwards.
So, just kind of twist it up real good.
Make sure to keep your top real good and you can kind of open this up and shape it out.
We need to twist it just a little bit tighter here.
Al least, I need to.
Make sure it's real good and tight.
There you go.
Alright.
And, there it is.
There's your paper flower, sure to impress.
And, she's going to be very happy and willing tonight.
My name is Robert Segundo and this is your paper flower.